(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
アイドルよ あてんしょんぷりーず！
Summer Idol Live
Idols, Attention Please!
アイドルよ あてんしょんぷりーず！
Summer Idol Live
Idols, Attention Please!
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade,
輝くんだよ
It's shining brightly.
呼び合い 声を 合図に
Calling out to each other, our voices as the signal.
パレ パレ パレ
Parade, parade, parade,
探しに行こう
Let's go and find it.
スタートは 何度だって
No matter how many times we start over.
いくぞーー！
Here we go!
Our Bright Parade
さくらみこ Solo ver.
作詞・作曲・編曲：堀江晶太
Our Bright Parade
Sakura Miko Solo ver.
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Shota Horie
ただ 独り言 綴った
I simply wrote down my monologues,
ただ 始まりだって 走った
And simply ran, thinking it was the beginning.
遠く 暗闇に 灯った
In the distant darkness, there was a light,
それは 眩しすぎた 名前
It was a name that shone far too brightly.
君を見つけたこと
Having found you
やさしさに甘えて もっと
Let me indulge more in your kindness
時間を溶かした 手を伸ばした
Melting time away, I reached out my hand
追いかけず 結び合った
Without chasing, we became tied together
ほら 今 まっさら 僕らになった
Look, now we've become a brand new "us"
パレ・パレ・パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along your frustrations and your affections
風 夢 羽ばたいてるさ
Wind, dreams, they are taking flight
鮮やかな 彩りは光
Vivid colors are the light
終わりなき 陽射し
Endless sunlight
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるのよ
I can be proud of having found you
ここから これから Our Bright Parade
From here on out, Our Bright Parade
まだ 頼りない歩調を
With still unsteady steps
歌は 恥ずかしくないよ
Singing is nothing to be ashamed of
誰も 解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary that no one can untie
いつか また 会おう マジナイ
A spell to meet again someday
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that began from zero that day
数えきれない言の葉
Countless words
飾るような 思いじゃないさ
It's not a feeling meant for show
ほら 今 僕らは 一つだよ
Look, now we are one
パレ・パレ・パレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's beautiful
許し合える 切な 夜はきらめく
Moments of mutual forgiveness, the night sparkles
雨・晴れ・晴れ また会いたい空
Rain, clear skies, the sky I want to see again
ふさわしい 旅路なら 君と歩くことさ
If it's a fitting journey, it's about walking with you
君と歩くことなんだ
It's about walking with you
「ただいま」を聞けば 「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
If I hear "I'm home," I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
パレ・パレ・パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
暗がりを 満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
What fills the darkness is you and me
パレ・パレ・パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along your frustrations and your affections
風 夢 羽ばたいてるさ
Wind, dreams, they are taking flight
鮮やかな 彩りは光
Vivid colors are the light
終わりなき 陽射し
Endless sunlight
君と 踏み込んでいこう 素敵な二重奏
Let's step forward with you into a wonderful duet
ここから これから Our Bright Parade
From here on out, Our Bright Parade
Our Bright Parade
I'm ready ハートコネクト
I'm ready, Heart Connect
約束の時間
The promised time
今日も元気に...
Energetically today as well...
あてんしょん ぷりーず！
Attention Please!
凛々しく かしこく エリートらしく
Dignified, clever, and like an elite
みんなのアイドルは 今日も今日とて KAWAII
Everyone's idol is cute today as always
よなよな オンステージ
Night after night on stage
アツい視線は スポットライトです ありがとうね
Your passionate gazes are my spotlights, thank you
ウェルカム スタンバイOK 宣誓 ごあいさつ
Welcome, standby OK, oath, greetings
本日ここに 開花宣言！
Today, right here, a blooming declaration!
あっちゅあっちゅ ぱーりーないつ
Hot, hot, party nights
とびきりの時間
An extra special time
夢中にさせてあげるから
Because I'll make you lose yourself in it
うれしたのしや 歌い明かそうよ
Joyful and fun, let's sing through the night
朝が来るまで
Until morning comes
あてんしょん ぷりーず！
Attention Please!
泣いてる姿は見せたくない
I don't want to show my crying face
努力もユウユウだよ　だってみんなのおかげ
Effort's a breeze, all thanks to everyone
キラキラ笑顔が
A sparkling smile,
思い出すたび毎日エールくれるから
cheers me up every day whenever I remember
サンキュ　今日はそのこと伝えに来たよ
Thank you, I came to tell you that today
だからたくさんいい表情しよう！
So let's make lots of great expressions!
まばたき注意
Don't blink!
しっかり焼き付けるね
I'll sear it into my memory
キミとハートコネクト　おわりたくないよ
Heart-connected with you, I don't want it to end
賛成のひとー？
Is everyone in favor?
アンコール　あっちゅあっちゅぱーりーないっ　とびきりの時間
Encore! A hot-hot party night, a special time
とっくにクセになってるはず
I'm sure you're already addicted
うれしたのしや歌い明かそうよ
Happy and fun, let's sing the night away
朝が来るまで
Until morning comes
あてんしょんぷりーず♪
Attention please♪
ぷりーず
Please!
盛り上がろうね
Let's get hyped!
The ぱーりーないっ♪
The party night♪
はーい、ということで
All right, so...
にゃっはろー！
Nyahallo!
エリート巫女のさくらみこでーす！
Elite Shrine Maiden Sakura Miko here!
今日は5周年記念ライブ、アイドルよ
Today is my 5th anniversary live,
あてんしょんぷりーず！に来てくれてありがとー！
"Idol yo, Attention Please!" Thanks for coming!
はい、ということで
Okay, so...
ハッシュタグはこちら！
Here's the hashtag!
ドーン！こちらね、たくさんスクショして、
Boom! Take lots of screenshots with this,
たくさんツイートしてね！よろしくお願いします！
and tweet them lots! Please look forward to it!
えー、ということで、ここからはゲストパートをやっていきたいと思います！
Uh, so, from here on, I'd like to do the guest part!
あ、そういえば、あ、これ、これ見てこれ！可愛い！
Oh, by the way, look at this! It's so cute!
これね、作ってもらいました、たい焼き！でっけー！
They made this for me, a Taiyaki! It's huge!
あ、写真撮った？あ、これね、スクショしてツイートしてくださいね！
Did you take a photo? Screenshot and tweet it!
はい、ということで、ここからは盛りだくさんのゲストパート！
Alright, so from here on, we have a jam-packed guest part!
そしてお披露目もあるので、最後まで見てねー！
And there's also a reveal, so watch until the end!
ポニーテールとシュシュ
Ponytail and Scrunchie
カレンダーより早くシャツの袖口まくって
Rolling up my shirt sleeves earlier than the calendar says
太陽が近づく気配僕の腕から衣替え
A sign of the sun approaching, I change clothes from my arms
青い海　波打ち際で君に会いたい
I want to meet you on the shore of the blue sea
裸足の水しぶき
Barefoot splashes
ポニーテール　揺らしながら風の中
With your ponytail swaying in the wind
君が走る　僕が走る　砂の上
You run, I run, on the sand
ポニーテール　揺らしながら振り向いた
With your ponytail swaying, you turned around
君の笑顔　僕の夏が始まる
Your smile, my summer begins
カレンダーより早く
Earlier than the calendar
シャツの袖口まくって
Rolling up my shirt sleeves
太陽が近づく気配
The sign of the sun approaching
僕の腕から届くよ
Reaches me from my arms
青い海　波打ち際で
At the blue sea's shore
君に会いたい
I want to see you
裸足の季節がやって来る
The season of bare feet is coming
好きなんて　言えるわけないよ
There's no way I can say I love you
後ろ姿に　気持ちをつぶやく
I whisper my feelings to your back
ポニーテール　切なくなる　夢の中
Ponytail, it makes me sad, in my dreams
君のすべて　僕のすべて　独り占め
All of you, all of me, I want it all to myself
ポニーテール　切なくなる　片想い
Ponytail, it makes me sad, unrequited love
目と目合えば　今はただの友達
When our eyes meet, we're just friends for now
束ねた長い髪
Your long hair tied up
水玉のシュシュ
A polka-dot scrunchie
恋のしっぽは　つかまえられない
The tail of love cannot be caught
触れたら　消えてゆく　幻
If touched, it fades away, an illusion
ポニーテール　ほどかないで　変わらずに
Ponytail, don't undo it, stay as you are
君は君で　僕は僕で　走るだけ
You're you, and I'm me, just running
ポニーテール　ほどかないで　いつまでも
Ponytail, don't undo it, forever
はしゃいでいる　君は少女のままで
In high spirits, you remain a girl
ララララララ…
La la la la la la...
Angelic Angel
作詞：畑 亜貴　作曲：森 慎太郎
Lyrics: Aki Hata  Composition: Shintaro Mori
ここはどこ？　待って言わないで
Where is this? Wait, don't tell me
わかってる　夢に見た熱い蜃気楼さ
I know, it's the hot mirage I saw in my dreams
君は誰？　なんて聞かないよ
Who are you? I won't ask that
わかってる　お互いの瞳が描いた出会い
I know, this encounter drawn by each other's eyes
遠ざかるほど光る一番星
The evening star that shines brighter the further away it gets
いつかそんな恋してみたかった
I wanted to fall in love like that someday
もういらないよ胸のブレーキは
I don't need the brakes in my heart anymore
見つめあうために生まれたふたりになってく
We are becoming two people born to gaze at each other
あぁ！　もしもは欲しくないのさ
Ah! I don't want "what ifs"
もっと　もっと　が好き！　Angel
I like "more, more"! Angel
翼をただの飾りにわしない
I won't let these wings be mere decorations
あぁ！　もしもは欲しくないけど
Ah! I don't want "what ifs", but
もっと　もっと　が好き！　Angel
I like "more, more"! Angel
明日じゃない　大事な時は今なんだと気がついて
It's not tomorrow, I realized the important time is now
心の羽ばたきは止まらない
The fluttering of my heart won't stop
ああ、お互いを
Ah, each other...
感じあえる出会い
An encounter where we can feel each other
さあ 踊りましょう
Come, let's dance
熱い炎をのせて
Carrying hot flames
そうさ 今夜のために
Yes, for tonight
全部懸けて
Betting everything
さあ 引き寄せて
Come, pull me closer
少し痛いくらい
To the point it's a bit painful
ひとすじの雫
A single streak of droplet
喜び染めこむ
Soaking in joy
ああ 今宵は
Ah, tonight
一夜限りにどこかへ
To somewhere just for one night
燃え尽きるまで
Until burning out
踊らなきゃダメさ
We must dance
ああ 今宵は
Ah, tonight
一夜限りにどこかへ
To somewhere just for one night
捕まえたら
If I catch you
そのまま強く
Just like that, strongly
抱きしめてと
Saying "Hold me tight"
囁いた
I whispered
愛おしい
My beloved
夢はまだ終わらない
The dream is not over yet
時間は止められない
Time cannot be stopped
としても
Even so
君と早く会いたかったよ
I wanted to see you sooner
届けたい言葉が
The words I want to deliver
踊り解けて
Unravel while dancing
Angel!
甘い夢は
Sweet dreams
欲しくないのさ
I don't want them
もっと好き Angel
Like you more, Angel
翼はただの
The wings are just
飾りにはしない
I won't make them mere ornaments
甘い夢は
Sweet dreams
欲しくないけど
I don't want them, but
もっと好き Angel
Like you more, Angel
明日じゃない
It's not tomorrow
大事なときは
The important time is
今なんだと
Saying "it's now"
気が付いて
Notice it
心の
The heart's
羽ばたきは止まらない
Flapping of wings won't stop
UNLIMITED IMPACT
作詞：真崎エリカ 作曲：本多友紀
Lyrics: Erika Masaki / Composition: Yuki Honda
視界全部
The entire view
奪うような
As if stealing it away
打ち付けるスコールの
In the midst of the pounding squall
中でも
Even so
きっとサヨナラへ
Surely, towards the goodbye
流れるのは
What flows is
意味分けた迷いだけだよ
Only the meaning-divided hesitation
ぬかるんだ現状に
In the muddy current situation
足元をとられて
Losing one's footing
憂鬱な空気が
The gloomy air
喉塞いでも
Even if it chokes the throat
この声は
This voice
絶やさないでしょう
Will probably not die out
この足は
These feet
止まらないでしょう
Will probably not stop
命の限り
As long as there's life
どうか全力で
Please, with all your might
射抜いてよ
Shoot through me
瞳で私を
Me, with your eyes
焼き付けていこう
Let's keep burning it in
それは約束の仕掛け
That's the mechanism of the promise
傷を痛がって
Feeling the pain of wounds
投げ出す程度の
And throwing it away
思いじゃない
It's not that kind of feeling
君は目撃者だよ
You are a witness
YES UNLIMITED IMPACT
強くなっていく向かい風に
In the headwind that grows stronger
自分自身じゃいたくないほど
To the point where I don't feel pain
ふっとさらわれ飛んでいくよ
I'll be swept away and fly off
ためらいも臆病さも
Both hesitation and cowardice
逆境はなくないって絶望を叩き
Saying adversity won't end, striking down despair
マイナス戦友は似合わない
Negative comrades-in-arms don't suit me
冷静ならあとは攻めるだけ
If I'm calm, all that's left is to attack
この夢は揺らがないでしょ 心の限り
This dream won't waver, right? As much as my heart allows
今を全力でいきたいよ 未完成な私で
I want to live now with all my might, as my incomplete self
胸を張っていこう これが選びたい進化だ
Let's walk with heads high, this is the evolution I want to choose
何があったってスタートをしたなら行くっきゃない
No matter what happens, once I've started, I've got to go
貫くよ いつだって
I'll see it through, always
お前ら！盛り上がってるかー！
Everyone! Are you fired up?!
まだまだ、盛り上がれるよな！
We can still get more fired up, right?!
みんな、行くぞー！
Everyone, let's go!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ずっと最大級を超えてく 刺激をあげる
I'll keep giving you thrills that exceed the maximum
そんな胸の中に火をつけてくよなドラマ
A drama like that, setting a fire in your heart
傷が塞がってしまうのを 待たずに挑むから
I'll take the challenge without waiting for wounds to heal
君が目撃してよ
You, witness it
どうか全力で抜いてよ 瞳で私を
Please, capture me with your eyes with all your might
焼き付けていこう これは約束の仕掛け
Let's burn it into memory, this is the promised setup
傷を痛がって投げ出す 程度の想いじゃない
My feelings aren't weak enough to quit because of pain
君は目撃者だよ
You are the witness
YES! UNLIMITED IMPACT!
見せてあげる エボリューション
I'll show you an evolution
ゴーアヘッド 未来全部
Go ahead, to the entire future
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
私 それともあの娘
Me? Or that girl?
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
星を巡るよ 純情
Pure heart traveling through stars
トライアングラー
Triangler
弱虫泣き虫強がって
Cowardly, crybaby, acting tough
まだいくんだと思う私
Thinking I'll still go on
愛するよりも 求めるより
More than loving, more than seeking
疑うほうが ずっとたやすい
Doubting is much easier
自分が悔しい
I'm frustrated with myself
痛いよ 味方だけど
It hurts, although I'm on your side
愛してないとか 守るけど
Saying I don't love you, but I'll protect you
そばにいないとか
Saying I'm not by your side
今すぐ タッチミー
Touch me right now
運命ならば つながせて
If it's fate, let us connect
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
私 それともあの娘
Me? Or that girl?
心揺らす言葉
Words that shake the heart
に乗せ　キミに　抱（い）たいだけ限界
Carrying... to you, I just want to hold you to the limit
妄想　裁きをきいて
Delusion, hear the judgment
後ろから　蹴り上げたら
If I kick you up from behind
むきだしの恋に　よろけた
Staggered by an exposed love
呼吸だけで精一杯
Just breathing is all I can do
迎えに来て　溺れてるから
Come to pick me up, because I'm drowning
痛いよ　前向きな嘘
It hurts, a positive lie
まに受けるのは　笑ってる声
Taking it seriously, the laughing voice
未来　もてあました
The future, I couldn't handle it
今すぐ　ハミング
Humming right now
理性なんて押し倒して
Pushing down my reason
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
私　それともあの子
Me? Or that girl?
涙まるで役立たず
Tears are completely useless
星を駆けるよ純情
Pure heart running through the stars
君は誰とキスをする
Who will you kiss?
私　それともあの子
Me? Or that girl?
たった一つ命を糧に
With only one life as nourishment
今　振りかざす感傷
Now, I brandish my sentimentality
たった一つ命を糧に
With only one life as nourishment
今　振りかざす感傷
Now, I brandish my sentimentality
アイドルはウーニャニャの件
作詞：秋元康 作曲：岡村弾
Regarding the Matter of Idols Being Uunyan-nya
Lyrics: Yasushi Akimoto / Composition: Dan Okamura
ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャー
ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャヨー
Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nyaa
Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya-yo
昔のアイドルなんてたって　スキャンダルはご法度さ（オキュッ）
Back then, idols couldn't have scandals, it was strictly forbidden (Okyut)
だけど今は人間じゃない　壁に耳あり障子に目あり
But nowadays idols aren't human, walls have ears and doors have eyes
あっという間に拡散しちゃう
It spreads in the blink of an eye
ネット炎上やってられない清純派
Online backlashes, being a pure idol is hard work
白黒つけずにスルーでごめん　ホントじゃないけどウソでもない
Sorry for ignoring without clarifying, it's not the truth but it's not a lie either
どっちつかずで七転八倒
Stuck in the middle, struggling through ups and downs
ヨロシク！
Nice to meet you!
ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャー
ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャ　ウーニャニャヨー
Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nyaa
Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya Uunyan-nya-yo
私たちだっておトイレも行くし
Even we go to the restroom
時にはルールも破ってしまう
And sometimes we even break the rules
ツチノコパンダよ味方して
Tsuchinoko Panda, be on our side!
サングラスかけ マスクをして
Wearing sunglasses and a mask
化けの皮 剥がれた私だときづいて
Notice me when my disguise comes off
プライベートはサインはダメ
No autographs in my private time
写真もダメと上から目線
No photos either, looking down on others
そんな自分が 好きじゃなくなる
I'm starting to dislike myself like that
裸の王様
The naked king
なぜか涙が溢れてくる
For some reason, tears are overflowing
私は何者? ここはどこなの?
Who am I? Where am I?
夢のような夢じゃない現実
A reality that's like a dream but not a dream
天国のような 地獄じゃない
It's like heaven, not like hell
地獄のような...地獄!
It's like hell... Hell!
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャウーニャよ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya-u-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャウーニャよ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya-u-nyanya
会えない時にも 浮かべるし
I can picture you even when we can't meet
人に言えない 秘密もあるわ
I have secrets I can't tell anyone
ツチノコパンダよ どっちなの! ホイ!
Tsuchinoko Panda, which one is it? Hoi!
アイドルの女の子 ろくに字も書けず
An idol girl, barely able to write
バカにならなきゃ やってられない
Can't get by unless I act like a fool
私、私 誰ですか? ウー!
Who, who am I? Woo!
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャウーニャよ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya-u-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya
ウーニャニャ ウーニャニャ ウーニャウーニャよ
U-nyanya, U-nyanya, U-nyanya-u-nyanya
アイドルだって 悩んでいるの
Even idols have worries
みんなが憧れる 世界じゃない
It's not the world everyone longs for
ツチノコパンダよ わかるでしょ? ホイ!
Tsuchinoko Panda, you understand, right? Hoi!
ツチノコパンダよ 味方して! ホイ!
Tsuchinoko Panda, take my side! Hoi!
恋になりたいAQUARIUM
Aquarium of Love-to-Be
空色のカーテン オープン
Sky-blue curtain open
海のゲート ウェルカム!
Welcome to the sea gate!
ユラユラ揺れながら 真珠の時計
Swinging back and forth, the pearl clock
君と私を 夢に誘い込むの
Inviting you and me into a dream
水槽で騒ぐ 騒いで跳ねる
In the aquarium, making a fuss and splashing
魚たちのパーティ
The fishes' party
呼んじゃったんだ 水の中でも
I called them, even underwater
息ができるの おまじないのせいかな
I can breathe, maybe because of a spell
街の喧騒は 気にしないしないで
Don't worry about the noise of the city
魚たちのパーティ 楽しもうか
Let's enjoy the fishes' party
とってもとっても 楽しそう
Looks very, very fun
プカプカ一緒に プカプカしちゃえば
If we float together, float along
いつもと違う私が 現れ
A different me from usual will appear
吐息が聞こえる 距離まで
To the distance where I can hear your breath
近づきたいな I miss you!
I want to get closer, I miss you!
アクアリウムで
In the aquarium
二人が出会うファンタジー
The fantasy where the two of us meet
不意にときめくの
Suddenly my heart flutters
それは恋の魔法
That's the magic of love
アクアリウムで
In the aquarium
気づいて 胸の奥 秘めてた
I realized, hidden deep in my heart
本物の気持ち
My true feelings
これから素直に なってみよう
From now on, I'll try to be honest
大好きはもう かくさない!
I won't hide my "I love you" anymore!
だって水の中 右にも左にも
Because underwater, to the right and left
下から上まで 上手く泳げるわ
From bottom to top, I can swim well
水深は浅いの? 青春は深いの?
Is the water shallow? Is youth deep?
魚たちはなんでも 知ってるよ
The fishes know everything
しっかりしっかり 楽しんで
Enjoy it thoroughly
最後は一緒に...
Finally, together...
泡になって
Become bubbles
また会えるね 私にキス
We'll meet again, kiss me
しちゃいま しちゃいたい しちゃいなよ
Do it, I want to do it, just do it
今すぐ I LOVE YOU
Right now, I love you
マリンブルーなら
If it's marine blue
ふたりは夢のシンフォニー
The two of us are a dream symphony
きっと奏でるの
Surely we'll play
甘い恋の奇跡
A sweet miracle of love
マリンブルーなら
If it's marine blue
初めてなのに怖くないんだもん
Even though it's the first time, I'm not afraid
本当に私
Really, I...
つぎから大胆になってみよう
...will try to be bolder next time
大好きよ もう隠さない
I love you, I won't hide it anymore
誘っちゃうんだ wow wow AQUARIUMで
I'll invite you wow wow at the Aquarium
誘っちゃうんだ wow wow 恋になりたい
I'll invite you wow wow I want to fall in love
Fantastic!
遊びましょう
Let's play
ぷかぷかで泡泡で
Floating and bubbling
見つめあっていたいな 大好き wow wow
I want to keep gazing at you, I love you wow wow
AQUARIUMで
At the Aquarium
ふたりが出会うファンタジー
The fantasy where the two of us meet
不意にときめくの
Suddenly my heart flutters
それは恋の魔法
That's the magic of love
AQUARIUMで
At the Aquarium
気づいて 胸の奥に秘めてた
Realize it, hidden deep in my heart
本当の気持ち
My true feelings
これから素直になって
From now on I'll be honest
つぎから大胆になってみよう
Will try to be bolder next time
大好きよ もう隠さない
I love you, I won't hide it anymore
Fantastic Love!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PAYA-PA
DISCO LADY DISCO LADY
DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION
SWEETIE 二人 踊りだそう
Sweetie, the two of us, let's start dancing
はじける BEAUTY LADY
Sparkling Beauty Lady
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn, a sweet dream
そっと 彩りたいの
I want to color it softly
グラマラスな唇
Glamorous lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Pink shimmering nails
ガラスの向こう側に
On the other side of the glass
映る素顔 シュールなDays
The face reflected, surreal days
キミだけにSO 見せていたい
I want to show only to you
心の中 瞳の奥
Deep in my heart, deep in my eyes
AH そばにいてほしいよ
Ah, I want you to be by my side
月のMIRROR BALL
The moon's mirror ball
照らされて
Illuminated
ねえ VIVIDな恋しましょう
Hey, let's have a vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Sparkling Sexy Beauty
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn, a sweet dream
そっと 彩る MY LOVE
Softly coloring my love
ほら 世界は変わる
See, the world changes
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PAYA-PA
ドラマティックな情熱
Dramatic passion
褪せないデジャヴ 見続けたくて
I want to keep seeing an unfading deja vu
カラフルなSWEETY STORY
A colorful Sweety Story
心深く 刻み込む
Carving it deep in my heart
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If I chant the spell of love
そう きっと 果てない空
Yes, surely the endless sky
星屑のSHOWERが
A shower of stardust
降り注ぐ
Will pour down
だから HAPPY STATION
So, the Happy Station
目指して...
Aiming for...
合わせて
Together
100%以上の愛
More than 100% love
揺るぎなく
Unwavering
ここにあると
Is right here
私思ってる
I believe
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PAYAPA
プログレッシブと
Progressive and
コンサバティブな自分
my conservative self
キミにありのままを
just as I am to you
好きでいて欲しい…と
I want you to love me...
願いは DISCO LADY
My wish is DISCO LADY
赤裸々 DEEP EMOTION
Naked DEEP EMOTION
MY DARLIN' もっと一緒に踊りましょう
MY DARLIN', let's dance together more
SECRET NIGHT 素敵な
SECRET NIGHT, a wonderful
ラブソングのデコレーション
Love song decoration
二人のハートで AH
With our two hearts, AH
奏で合わせて
Let's play together
MY DARLIN' ねえ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
MY DARLIN', hey, let's have a vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Popping SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢
Reborn in a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE
Softly coloring MY LOVE
ほら 世界は変わる
Look, the world is changing
CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PAYAPA
みこち、5周年おめでとう！
Mikochi, happy 5th anniversary!
お祝いに来ました、そらあずです！
We came to celebrate, we're SoraAz!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
いつもの夏と違うんだ
This summer is different from usual
誰も気づいていないけど
Though nobody has noticed yet
日差しの強さだとか
Like the intensity of the sunlight
花の色の鮮やかさとか
Or the brightness of the flower's colors
何度も季節は巡って
The seasons have passed many times
どこかに忘れていたもの
Things I had forgotten somewhere
誰かを好きになる
Falling in love with someone
切ない入口を
At that painful entrance
You know
オレンジ色の
The orange-colored
眩しいワンピース
bright one-piece dress
サイドボブで
with a side bob
太陽が似合うのは君だ
the one the sun suits is you
ルイボスティーを飲みながら
While drinking rooibos tea
なぜ一人微笑む
why are you smiling alone?
テーブルの下さりげなく
Under the table, casually
サンダル脱ぎ捨てていた
you had kicked off your sandals
裸足になってどうするつもり
What do you intend to do barefoot?
そのままどこかへ歩いてゆくの
Are you going to walk off somewhere like that?
ねえ 何をしたいんだ
Hey, what do you want to do?
行動が予測できないよ
I can't predict your actions
人目も気にせずに
Without worrying about others' eyes
気ままでそう君にいつも
Selfishly, yes, by you always
振り回されて
Being jerked around
呆れたり疲れたり
Being amazed or getting tired
それでも君に恋をしてる
Even so, I'm in love with you
近くにいつも大勢
Always many people nearby
いるよ男友達
male friends are there
その中の一人が僕だ
one of them is me
悔しいけどしょうがない
it's frustrating, but it can't be helped
告白もしてないし
I haven't even confessed
今の距離感が心地いい
the current distance feels good
普通で楽なんだ
it's normal and easy
それなら僕も裸足になって
If that's the case, I'll go barefoot too
一緒にどこでも歩いてゆくよ
And walk anywhere with you
なんたって付き合うさ
After all, I'll go along
愛おしさが背中を押すんだ
My love pushes me forward
自分の気持ちは隠したまま
While keeping my feelings hidden
そう君といると素直になれる
Yes, when I'm with you, I can be honest
欲しいものは前
What I want is in front of me...
胸にある
In my heart
いつかはちゃんと話せるかな
Will I be able to tell you properly one day?
いつもの夏と違うんだ
This summer is different from the usual
君は気づいてないけど
Although you haven't noticed
振っている回数も
The number of times I wave
触れた指の引っ込め方を
And how I pulled my fingers back after touching
幾度も鏡を見ながら
Looking in the mirror many times
寝癖も直してきたこと
Fixing my bedhead before coming
苦しくなるくらい
So much it's painful
すべてがぎこちない
Everything feels awkward
I know
裸足になってどうするつもり
What are you planning to do barefoot?
そのままどこかへ歩いて行くの
Are you just going to walk off somewhere like that?
ねえ 何をしたいんだ？
Hey, what do you want to do?
行動が予測できないよ
I can't predict your actions
人の目気にせずに
Without caring about people's stares
気まぐれでしょ 君にいつも
You're so whimsical, I'm always...
振り回されて
...being swung around by you
呆れたり疲れたり
Being amazed or getting tired
それでも君に恋をしてる
But even so, I'm in love with you
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
Stirring up the media with an invincible smile
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
I want to know your secret, so mysterious
抜けてるところさえ彼女のエリア
Even her clumsy parts are her territory
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You, who are perfect and a liar
天才的なアイドル様
You're a genius-like idol
アイドル
作詞・作曲: Ayase
Idol
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
今日何食べた？
What did you eat today?
好きな本は？
What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you go out, where do you go?
何も食べてない
I haven't eaten anything
それは内緒
That's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what I'm asked, I dodge it
そう淡々と だけど燦々と
So indifferently, yet so brilliantly
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
The secrets that seem visible but aren't, taste like honey
あれもないないない
That's not there, not there, not there
これもないないない
This isn't there, not there, not there
好きなタイプは？
What's your type?
相手は？
Who's the partner?
さあ答えて
Come on, answer me
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really understand things like falling in love with someone"
嘘か本当か知り得ない そんな言葉にまた一人落ちる
Unknowable whether it's a lie or the truth, yet another person falls for those words
また好きにさせる
Making them fall in love again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone's eyes are stolen away
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You're the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない
Never to appear again
一番星の生まれ変わり
The reincarnation of the brightest star
ああ その笑顔で「愛してる」で
Ah, with that smile, with that "I love you"
誰も彼も虜にしていく
You're making everyone your captive
その瞳が その言葉が
Those eyes, those words
嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
Even if it's a lie, it's perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々はハナからおまけです
We're just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
We're just the background character B for the star
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to that girl
洒落臭い 妬み嫉妬なんてないわけがない
How annoying, there's no way there isn't envy and jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
This isn't a joke, that's why it's unforgivable
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
I can't forgive you if you're not perfect
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't acknowledge anyone except you who are stronger than anyone
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes and worships you
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest and invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない
No weaknesses can be found
一番星を宿している
Bearing the brightest star within you
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
You must never, ever show your weak points
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing the parts people don't want to know
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
You must be one and only, or I won't have it
それこそ本物のアイ
That's what true love is
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Thrilling the media with a trademark smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Keeping this secret hidden to the end
「愛してる」って嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on the lie of "I love you"
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own kind of love
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Maria
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, a lie is an extraordinary love
誰かに愛されたことも 誰かのこと愛したこともない
I've never been loved by anyone, nor have I ever loved anyone
そんな私の嘘がいつか本当になること信じてる
I believe that my lie will one day become the truth
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
I will surely get everything one day
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
Because I'm a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと
In my true self, everyone...
ちゃんと愛したいから
...I want to love you properly
嘘つくの、この言葉が
Lying, these words...
いつか本当になる日を願って
Wishing for the day they'll become true
それでもまだ、君と君にだけは言えずに
Even so, I still couldn't say it to you and only you,
いたけど
...but I still...
ああ、やっと言えた、これは
Ah, I finally said it, this...
絶対嘘じゃない
...is definitely not a lie,
愛してる
I love you.
はい、ということで、ライブは残すところ、あと1曲となるんですが、
All right, and with that, there's only one song left in the live performance,
ゲストパートの大トリを、務めさせて頂いた、務めて頂いた、
...and for the grand finale of the guest segment, we had...
星街すいせいさんと、告知タイムの、いきたいと思います！
...Hoshimachi Suisei-san join us, so let's move on to the announcement segment!
星街すいせいです。さくらみこさん、この度は5周年おめでとうございます！
I'm Hoshimachi Suisei. Sakura Miko-san, congratulations on your 5th anniversary!
ありがと、すいせいさん！
Thank you, Suisei-san!
私も一番最後に、一緒にね、アイドル歌わせていただきまして、
At the very end, I got to sing 'Idol' together with you,
究極のアイドルね！
The ultimate idol song!
はい。とっても楽しかったです！
Yes. It was so much fun!
よし、撮りますか、これ。アイドルらしくね！
Okay, shall we take a picture? Like idols!
アイドルらしくね！
Like idols!
はい、こびタイム！
Okay, flirtatious time!
はい。こび、はにゃ？
Okay. Flirt, hannya?
はい。こび、はにゃ！はい、こび...
Okay. Flirt, hannya! Okay, flirt...
はわわ...
Hawawa...
はわわ...にゃにゃん！
Hawawa... Nyan nyan!
にゃにゃん！アイドルにゃにゃん！
Nyan nyan! Idol nyan nyan!
私が前でいいんですか？
Is it okay if I'm in front?
あ、いいですよ、じゃ、みこちゃん
Oh, sure. Well then, Miko-chan...
はい、どうぞ
Yes, go ahead.
え、じゃあ...何ですか？
Eh, well... what is it?
ピース！
Peace!
ピース！ピース！
Peace! Peace!
あ、やって。私乗るわ、それ。それ、あれやってよ
Ah, do it. I'll join in. Do that, that thing.
何？
What?
あれやって、手出してよ
Do that, put your hand out.
あ、はい、はい、はい
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
ちょこっとすいちゃん！
Little Sui-chan!
はい、可愛い！はい、可愛い！
Yes, cute! Yes, cute!
はい、ということでね。はい、皆さん喜んだところで
All right, and with that. Okay, now that everyone's happy...
告知がありますよね！
There are announcements, right?
はい、告知があるということで、やっていきたいと思います！
Yes, since there are announcements, let's get into them!
まずはグッズの告知、こちら！ドン！
First, announcements for the merchandise, here! Bam!
さくらみこ5周年記念グッズが出ます！
Sakura Miko 5th Anniversary merchandise is coming out!
めでたい！わあ！
Congratulations! Wow!
すごい！可愛い！可愛い！
Amazing! So cute! So cute!
ということで、え、じゃあ一つ一つ、紹介していこうと思います。まずは、こちら！
So, well, let's introduce them one by one. First of all, this!
はい、こちらがですね、5周年記念の、パブミラーとなっております
Yes, this here is the 5th Anniversary pub mirror.
パブミラーって何なんですか？
What exactly is a pub mirror?
パブミラーは、あの、鏡にイラストがピッとあって、ピカピカして素敵記念、みたいな
A pub mirror is, you know, a mirror with an illustration on it, and it's all shiny and wonderful for the anniversary.
何も分かりませんでした
I understood nothing.
すごい豪華なんですね！
It's really luxurious!
すごい豪華なミラーで。リッチな感じに見える。リッチなミラーですね
It's a really gorgeous mirror. It looks rich. A rich mirror.
はい。こちら、おるだん先生が、みこの水着をね、デザインしてもらって、
Yes. Ordan-sensei designed Miko's swimsuit for this,
とっても可愛い、イラストとなっております
...and it's a very cute illustration.
イラスト。ちょっとムチッとしてますね
The illustration. It's a bit 'thicc', isn't it?
黙れ！
Shut up!
お前だよ！
It's you!
はい。こちら、ぜひ買ってください！
Yes. Please be sure to buy this!
そして、なんとこちら、ドン！
And then, look at this, bam!
はい、マグチのぬいぐるみが、出るんですね！
Yes, a Maguchi plushie is coming out!
え、ついにこの世に具現化したんですね！
Eh, it's finally been manifested in this world!
具現化しました。なんと。しかも、あの、マシュマロみたいに、もちもちって感じでね
Manifested, indeed. And, well, it's squishy like a marshmallow.
もちもち。もちもち、むちむちって感じで、とっても可愛く出来上がってるので
Squishy. It feels squishy and soft, and it turned out really cute.
すいちゃんもぬいぐるみ好きだからね、あげるね、じゃ、たこ焼き出そうかな、たこ焼き
Sui-chan likes plushies too, so I'll give you one. Maybe I'll put out a Takoyaki one too.
ペアでね
As a pair.
ペアでね。ぜひ買ってくださいね
As a pair. Please buy them, okay?
出るか分かりませんけど。はい
I don't know if they'll actually come out. Yes.
はい、そしてこちら、ドン！
Okay, and next is this, bam!
はい、こちらが、ひっかける見守り35Pマスコットと言いまして
Yes, this is called the 'Hanging Watchful 35P Mascot'.
35P！
35P!
そう、これ、35Pのちっちゃいので、これがデスクトップとかの、ちょこんって乗る感じになっております
Yes, this is a little 35P, and it's designed to sit snugly on your desktop and such.
なるほど、可愛い！
I see, how cute!
可愛らしいですね。これ、ホロライブで流行らへんかな、これね
It's adorable. I wonder if this will become a trend in Hololive.
お買い求めください！はい、ぜひ、可愛いので皆さん、ぜひ買ってください
Please purchase one! Yes, definitely, they're cute so everyone, please buy them.
そして、なんと、なんと、こちら、ドドン！
And then, look, look at this, ba-bam!
初のEP、ハートコネクト、出ます！
My first EP, 'heart♡connect', is coming out!
みこもついにCDが出るよ、すいちゃん！
Miko's finally getting a CD too, Sui-chan!
わあ、すごいですよ！
Wow, that's amazing!
おめでとうございます！すごいですね！何曲ですか、何曲？
Congratulations! That's wonderful! How many songs are on it?
こちらはですね、7曲！
This one has... 7 songs!
7曲！なんと、ラッキーセブンです！
7 songs! Wow, Lucky Seven!
わざとらしい！ぜひ皆さん買って下さい！
How staged! Everyone, please buy it!
買って！はい！
Buy it! Yes!
こちらね、ぐちこ先生に描き下ろしていただいた、ジャケットとなっておりまして、
This jacket was newly illustrated by Guchico-sensei,
めちゃくちゃね、あの、夏らしくて、可愛いし、
...and it's very summery and cute,
あの、帽子にね、3と5って書いてあるの、英語で
...and it has '3' and '5' written on the hat in English.
いいですね！みこさんらしいですね！
That's nice! It's very Miko-san!
そう、とってもアイドルらしい、アイドル、アイドルのCDとなっております
Yes, it's a very idol-like, idol-themed CD.
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
お願いいたしまーす！
Please do!
はい、そしてこちら、活動5周年記念フルセット特典として、
Yes, and here, as a bonus for purchasing the full 5th Anniversary set,
箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入り、おるだん先生描き下ろしアナザージャケットカードが付いてきます！
...you'll get an Ordan-sensei illustrated 'Another Jacket' card with a foil-stamped replica signature and message!
うわあ、すごいですね！
Whoa, that's amazing!
そうですね。あの...
That's right. Um...
CDにスッと差し込める形となっておりまして...
It's designed to slip right into the CD case...
もうねCDはね、あの歌詞カードの中にも色んな特典がありまして、動画のやつとか。
As for the CD, the lyrics card contains various bonuses, like videos and such.
いろいろあるんで、これCD買わないとね。
There's so much in there, you really have to buy the CD.
わからないよね。
You never know what you'll find.
2枚とか3枚とかさ、飾ってくれたらさ、いいよね。
It'd be nice if you could display two or three of them.
っていうことで出しております。
So, that's what we're releasing.
はい、ぜひ皆さん、あの単品でもね、お買い求めください。
Yes, everyone, please consider buying them, even individually.
ください。
Please do.
そして、なんと、あの数量限定も出ます。
And believe it or not, there's a limited edition coming out too.
なんと！
No way!
数量限定は直筆メッセージがつきます。
The limited edition comes with a handwritten message.
2とかね、Vとかね。
Like '2' or 'V' and things like that.
何枚書くんですか？
How many are you going to write?
いっぱい。
A whole lot.
いっぱいです。ぜひ買ってください。
Tons of them. Please be sure to buy it.
今回はなんと、いっぱい書きますのでね、皆さんぜひこのあと発売なのでダッシュしてくださいね。
I'll be writing so many this time, so everyone, please dash to get it when it goes on sale soon!
はい、よろしくお願いいたします。
Yes, thank you for your support.
そして...
And next...
このあと、アルバムに収録されているさくらが手がけたハムさん作曲の新曲をお披露目します。
Next, I'll be premiering a new song from my album, with lyrics by me and music by Ham-san.
なんと！お披露目！
Wow! A premiere!
そしてなんと、歌詞、みこ初めて作詞、頑張りました。
And believe it or not, I, Miko, worked hard on writing lyrics for the first time.
なんと、あのみこさんが！
Wow, THE Miko-san did?!
はい、ま、ハム先生にもね、ちょっと助けてもらったけど...
Yes, well, Ham-sensei did help me out a little bit...
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
アッチアッチ、アツイね、アツイね。
It's hot, hot! Getting fired up, isn't it?
アッチアッチ、アチュイみたいな。
Hot, hot, like 'achui'!
本当にね、35Pに対する、活動に対する、これまでのいろんなのをふんだんに込めた曲となっておりますので、ぜひ聞いてください。
It's a song filled with all my feelings for the 35P and my activities up until now, so please listen to it.
私も少し歌っておりますので、ご注目ください。
I'm singing a little bit too, so please listen for that.
はい、すいちゃんもね、そう、手伝っていただきましたと。
Yes, Sui-chan also helped me out.
はい。
Yes.
はい、ということで、それじゃあ、着替えてこようと思います。
All right, with that, I'm going to go get changed.
はい。
Okay.
それでは、いきますよ。失礼いたします。
Well then, here we go. Excuse us.
いけ！失礼いたします。
Go! Excuse us.
さいなら、さいなら。えい、ほい。
Bye-bye, bye-bye. Hey, ho!
着替えよう。やめて。うぇい。
Let's change! Stop it! Wey!
アワーツリー
作詞：さくらみこ／ハム　作曲・編曲：ハム
Awa Tree
Lyrics: Sakura Miko / Ham  Composition/Arrangement: Ham
ねぇ 思い出したんだ
Hey, I remembered
そっと涙した日を
The day I shed tears quietly
さぁ 数えてみようか
Come, shall we count them?
これまで起こした奇跡を
The miracles we've made until now
ひとつ とまらない足で
One, with feet that won't stop
ふたつ 越えていく夢も
Two, even the dreams we surpass
みっつ つながる絆は
Three, the bonds that connect us
君とひろげてきたんだよ
I've expanded them with you
何度でも咲くように
So that they bloom again and again
続いてくこの物語 "ストーリー"
This story that continues
まだ見たことのない
The scenery I haven't seen yet
景色を探しにゆこう
Let's go find it
花ひとつずつが小さくても
Even if each flower is small
ほら
Look
支え合えたら桜になれるよ
If we support each other, we can become a cherry blossom
ぼくらが繋いだ大きな木は まだ
The big tree we've connected is still...
これからも春風に乗って伸びてくのさ
...going to grow, riding on the spring breeze from now on
ひとつ 涙こぼれたら
One, if tears fall
ふたつ 両手を叩いて
Two, clap both hands
みっつ 数え始めよう
Three, let's start counting
君といれば大丈夫
With you, everything's alright
弱音と本音で泣いたり
Crying with weaknesses and true feelings
諦めかけた分岐 "ルート" も
Even the paths where I almost gave up
振り返って笑うように
So that I can look back and laugh
ずっと強くなれたんだ
I was able to become much stronger
枝ひとつずつじゃくじけそうでも
Even if I'm about to break with just one branch
ほら
Look
支え合えたら大樹になれるよ
If we support each other, we can become a great tree
手と手を合わせた形は花びら
The shape of our hands joined together is a petal
この気持ち言葉すら越えて届けるのさ
I'll deliver this feeling, even beyond words
冴えない私を好きになってくれたこと
The fact that you came to like the uncool me
これからも後悔なんてさせないよ 見ててね
I won't let you regret it from now on either, so watch me
意地を張ってた頃よりも
More than back when I was being stubborn
強く大きくなったでしょう？
I've become stronger and bigger, haven't I?
もっと君を支える側になりたいから
Because I want to be more on the side of supporting you
空に願う星 涙をあずけて
Wishing on a star in the sky, entrusting my tears.
そろそろぼくも 一歩踏みこむよ
It's about time I take a step forward too.
ぼくらが育てた大きな木は ほら
Look, the big tree we grew together...
こんなにも陽だまりのような場所になったよ
Has become such a sun-drenched place.
La La La...
ねえ 見せてくれたよね
Hey, you showed me, didn't you?
こんなに素敵な未来
Such a wonderful future.
さあ まだまだ続くよ
Now, it's still going to continue.
これからもずっとありがとう
Thank you for everything from now on too.
ねえ 思い出したんだ そっと 涙した日を
Hey, I remembered. The day I quietly cried.
さあ 数えてみようか これまで証した奇跡を
Now, shall we try counting? The miracles we've proven until now.
このあと22時 プレミア公開
Premiere at 22:00 tonight.
LIVEみてくれてありがとうにぇ☆ ついに6年目のみこです。
Thank you for watching the LIVE! I'm Miko, finally in my 6th year.
「さくらみこ」としてこれからも みんなと笑顔で生きるぞ！！
As "Sakura Miko," I'll continue to live with everyone with a smile!!
もっといっしょに夢を咲かせていこう 35P、いつもありがとう！
Let's make more dreams bloom together. 35P, thank you as always!
これからもずっと、ありがとう
Forever from now on, thank you.